question_data = [
    {
        "question": "Which country does not share a border with Czechia",
        "correct_answer": "Slovenia",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which European country is the number 1 tourist destination in the world?",
        "correct_answer": "France",
    },
    {
        "question": "In which European Country can you find the Acropolis?",
        "correct_answer": "Greece",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most densely populated country in Europe?",
        "correct_answer": "Monaco",
    },
    {
        "question": "In which European countries city can you find the EU headquarters?",
        "correct_answer": "Belgium",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Countries city is the most populous city in Europe?",
        "correct_answer": "Turkey",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which European country has the longest coastline?",
        "correct_answer": "Norway",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is not part of the Balkans?",
        "correct_answer": "Poland",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country in Europe does not have a monarchy?",
        "correct_answer": "Finland",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has won the most Eurovision titles?",
        "correct_answer": "Ireland",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which European country’s flag has the most different colours on it?",
        "correct_answer": "Croatia",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Countries language is the most commonly spoken first language in Europe?",
        "correct_answer": "Germany",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these countries’ capitals is spelled the same in its native language"
                    " as in English? [Italy, Austria, Poland, Spain]",
        "correct_answer": "Spain",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the smallest country in Europe?",
        "correct_answer": "Vatican City",
    }
]
